MacKaye Family papers ML-5
Rauner Special Collections Library
- Benton MacKaye, 1880-1976; 21
  - Box: 173, 1890-1967 (Box 173)
    Box: 173
    - Maps: "Old Maps- MA Mid-American Series", 1965 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Maps: Squannacook, undated (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Maps: Geology Trips - Tennessee, 1935 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Maps: "Boundry Work, 1965-1967 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Maps: Montachusett Region, 1967 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Maps: Original Maps and Drawings, D[epartment] of L[abor] Report, undated (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Maps: Lumber Report, 1921 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Maps: Shirley, Mass, 1945 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Maps: Wartime Migration in the United States with charts, 1944 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Maps: Original "The Nation" on World Community Flow, 1926 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Maps: White River, Mo, with data, 1939 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Report: American Labor and Regional Planning, undated (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Report: "The Case Method in Forest Organization", undated (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Report: "Classification of the Forest Region of the United States", undated (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Maps: "A Cross Section of New England in 1753", undated (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Maps: Evolution Curve, undated (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Notes: "The Fight of the Federal Government to Make A Region Of A River", undated (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Notes: Lay-Out of Florida, Mass, undated (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Data: Forest, undated (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Notes: Forest Projects, undated (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Notes: Forest Miscellaneous, undated (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - Articles: Forest Service, undated (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - Legislation, undated (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - Notes: Wages, Lumber etc., undated (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - Bulletin: Massachusetts Forestry Association 151, undated (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Notes: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 173, Folder 26)
    - Notes: "National Forestry", undated (Box 173, Folder 27)
    - Writing: "The National Forest Timber Policy", undated (Box 173, Folder 28)
    - Notes: "Six Months in the White House" by Frank B. Carpenter, undated (Box 173, Folder 29)
    - Notes: "Physical Geography" by William Morris Davis, undated (Box 173, Folder 30)
    - Notes: "The Living Thoughts of Thomas Jefferson" by John Dewey, undated (Box 173, Folder 31)
    - Notes: "Farm to Table", undated (Box 173, Folder 32)
    - Notes: Maine Trip, undated (Box 173, Folder 33)
    - Notes: "The New Exploration and the Appalachian Trail", undated (Box 173, Folder 34)
    - Notes: On Railroads, undated (Box 173, Folder 35)
    - Notes: On Russia, undated (Box 173, Folder 36)
    - Notes: "A Substitute for the Economy of Wealth ", undated (Box 173, Folder 37)
    - Report: Pike Report, undated (Box 173, Folder 38)
    - Report: Preliminary Report on the Wood Products Industry, undated (Box 173, Folder 39)
    - Writing: "A Project in Conservation", undated (Box 173, Folder 40)
    - Writing: "Re: Marshall's Speech", undated (Box 173, Folder 41)
    - Writing: "Social Engineering" Outline for Possible Course, undated (Box 173, Folder 42)
    - Notes: "Social Mechanism", undated (Box 173, Folder 43)
    - Writing: "Statement on Skyline Highway", undated (Box 173, Folder 44)
    - Report: "Status of Forestry in the U.S.", undated (Box 173, Folder 45)
    - Writing: "Student Exercises", undated (Box 173, Folder 46)
    - Writing: "A Suggested Clearing House For Radicals", undated (Box 173, Folder 47)
    - Writing: " A Theory of Forest Management", undated (Box 173, Folder 48)
    - Writing: "Theory of Forest Regulation as Applied to White Pine Boxboard Lands in Southern New England", undated (Box 173, Folder 49)
    - Writing: "Thoreau on ‘Ktaadn'", undated (Box 173, Folder 50)
    - Writing: "To All Who Love Wilderness: Letter to the Adirondack Moose River Committee", undated (Box 173, Folder 51)
    - Writing: "Letter to the Committee on Agriculture, House of Representative" on acquiring National Forests, undated (Box 173, Folder 52)
    - Writing: "To Recapture Prosperity, undated (Box 173, Folder 53)
    - Notes: Trips to Study Ground Cover, undated (Box 173, Folder 54)
    - Writing: MS "The Non-Industrial Services" Fragment, undated (Box 173, Folder 55)
    - Report: Working Plan Report for the Forest Land of the McDowell Memorial, undated (Box 173, Folder 56)
    - Writing: Boyhood School Notes, undated (Box 173, Folder 57)
    - Writing: Boyhood Writings, undated (Box 173, Folder 58)
    - Writing: Poem, 1890 (Box 173, Folder 59)
    - Writing: Diary pages, 1891 (Box 173, Folder 60)
    - Writing: RBC (Rambling Boy's Club) Constitution, 1891 (Box 173, Folder 61)
    - Writing: Constitution for "The Cosmopolitan Organization, 1892-1893 (Box 173, Folder 62)
    - Writing: MS Notebook "Geographical Hand Book Containing Detailed Information Regarding All Parts of The World", 1893 (Box 173, Folder 63)
    - Writing: Expedition One-Nine, 1893 (Box 173, Folder 64)
    - Writing: "Report on the Operations of the Goodyear Lumber Company of Pennsylvania", undated (Box 173, Folder 65)
    - Writing: Civil Service Examination for Forestry, 1903-1910 (Box 173, Folder 66)
    - Writing: Log of Camp Moosilauke, 1904 (Box 173, Folder 67)
    - Data: Franconia, New Hampshire Forestry Survey, 1906 (Box 173, Folder 68)
    - Writing: "Pennichuck Valuation Surveys" with data, 1906-1907 (Box 173, Folder 69)
    - Writing: "A Working Plan for the Woodlands of the Pennichuck Water Co.", 1906 (Box 173, Folder 70)
    - Writing: "Reports on the Examination of Woodland", 1907 (Box 173, Folder 71)
    - Writing: Fitzwilliam, New Hampshire Forest Survey with data, 1908 (Box 173, Folder 72)
    - Writing: Memo to the US House of Representatives' Committee on Agriculture, 1908 (Box 173, Folder 73)
    - Notes: US Forest Service Field Notes, 1907-1909 (Box 173, Folder 74)
  - Box: 174, 1897-1908 (Box 174)
    Box: 174
    - Writing: "Record of Field Work, Petersham, 1908-1909 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Report: Conspirators Club, 1909 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Data: Log Rules, 1909 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Writing: "Report on the Forest lands of Witherbee, Sherman & Co.", 1909 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 1", undated (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 1a", 1908 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 2", 1907-1908 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 2", circ 1907-1908 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 4", undated (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 5", undated (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 6", undated (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 7", undated (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 7a", 1909 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 8", undated (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Writing: Lecture Notes "Forestry 9", 1909 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Notes: Teaching Forestry Courses, 1907-1908 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Notes: Plant Physiology, undated (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Notes: Tree Physiology, undated (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Notes: Tree Planting, undated (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Notes: Reports by Forestry Students, 1907 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - Writing: Student Class Notes for Economics 6, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 21)
    - Writing: Academic Paper for Economics 6 "Improvements in Transportation", 1900 (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - Writing: Report for Economics 6 "The Commercial Policy of Europe as Compared with that of the United States 1846-1900" (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - Writing: Two Briefs for English C, 1898/99 (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - Writing: Academic Paper "Forensic No.1" for English C, 1899 (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - Notes: Class Notes "Geography A", 1897 (Box 174, Folder 26)
    - Writing: Report #1 "Effects of the Drainage of the English Midland Lowland" for Geology 7, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 27)
    - Notes: Class Notes for Government 4, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 28)
    - Notes: Class Notes for History 12, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 29)
    - Notes: Class Notes for History 13, 1897-1898 (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - Notes: Class Notes for Botany 1, 1903-1904 (Box 174, Folder 31)
    - Notes: Class Notes for Botany 9, undated (Box 174, Folder 32)
    - Notes: Class Notes for Forestry 5, 1904-1905 (Box 174, Folder 33)
    - Notes: Class Notes for Forestry 6, undated (Box 174, Folder 34)
    - Notebook: Geology 5/Geography A, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 35)
    - Notebook: Geology 7, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 36)
    - Notebook: Geology 7, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 37)
    - Notebook: Geology 11, 1900 (Box 174, Folder 38)
  - Box: 175, 1910-1916 (Box 175)
    Box: 175
    - Notebook: Botany 2, undated (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: Botany 9, undated (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: Data and Charts, undated (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Notes: Miscellaneous by Mabel F. Abbott, undated (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Writing: Outline of Work on Forest Management by M.F.Abbott, undated (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Writing: MS "Forest Management" by M.F.Abbott Excerpts, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Writing: Typescript and MS"Forest Management" by M.F.Abbott Excerpts, undated (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Writing: Notes on "The Ballinger-Pinchot Investigation Committee" by M.F.Abbott, undated (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Writing: "Conservation News" by M.F.Abbott, undated (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Writing: "Conservation News" by M.F.Abbott, 1909 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Writing: "Conservation News" by M.F. Abbott, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Writing: Articles for "Conservation News" by M.F. Abbott, undated (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Introduction, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Part I, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Part II, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Part IV, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Part V, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Writing: MS "A Brief History of Conservation" by M.F.Abbott, Notes, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - Writing: Benton MacKaye "Four to Four: Supreme Court vs. The Forester", undated (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - Writing: Benton MacKaye "Re. Ballinger-Pinchot Committee", undated (Box 175, Folder 25)
    - Writing: Benton MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - Writing: Summery of W.B.Greeley's Report: "Some Economic Aspects of the Lumber Industry", 1910 (Box 175, Folder 27)
    - Writing: Harvard Class of 1900 Biography, 1910 (Box 175, Folder 28)
    - Writing: Notes on R.T.Fisher's "Skeleton of Working Plan", 1910 (Box 175, Folder 29)
    - Writing: "Working Plan for the Rhododendron Reservation of the Appalachian Mountain Club", 1910 (Box 175, Folder 30)
    - Writing: Excerpts from the Weeks Act, 1911 (Box 175, Folder 31)
    - Writing: "A Digest of the Relation of Forests to Stream Flow", 1911-1912 (Box 175, Folder 32)
    - Writing: "Forest Cover on the Watershed Examined by the Geological Survey in the White Mountains, NH", 1913 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    - Writing: Re. Poindexter Alaskan Bill including Newspaper Clippings and Data, 1913 (Box 175, Folder 34)
    - Writing: "The Relation of Forests to Stream Flow", 1913 (Box 175, Folder 35)
    - Writing: Disarmament Bulletin, 1914 (Box 175, Folder 36)
    - Writing: Drawing on River Regulation, 1914 (Box 175, Folder 37)
    - Writing: Interstate Commerce Bill, undated (Box 175, Folder 38)
    - Writing: On Settlement of the Northeastern Lake States, 1915-1916 (Box 175, Folder 39)
    - Writing: "Tentative Plan for Forest Service participation in Conservation Exhibit", 1915 (Box 175, Folder 40)
    - Writing: Trust Bill, 1915 (Box 175, Folder 41)
    - Writing: Directories, 1915-1916 (Box 175, Folder 42)
    - Writing: " The Castle - A Memorial to William Payson MacKaye ", 1916 (Box 175, Folder 43)
    - Writing: Estimates of US Land Areas, 1916 (Box 175, Folder 44)
    - Notes: Notes on the IWW/Forest Camps, 1916 (Box 175, Folder 45)
    - Writing: Oregon/California Lands Information, 1916 (Box 175, Folder 46)
    - Writing: "Recreational Possibilities of Public Forests", 1916 (Box 175, Folder 47)
    - Writing: River Regulation Work, 1916 (Box 175, Folder 48)
    - Writing: "Settling Timber Lands", 1916 (Box 175, Folder 49)
  - Box: 176, 1917-1920 (Box 176)
    Box: 176
    - Writing: Typescript "Colonization of Timberlands" pages 1-143, 1917 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Writing: Typescript " Colonization of Timberlands" The Darrington Project pages 144-197, 1917 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Writing: Typescript "Colonization of Timberlands" pages 192-272, 1917 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Writing: Canadian Data and Notes, 1918 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Writing: Crosser Bill/Colonization Project, 1916-1917 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Writing: "After the War Colonization", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Writing: "The Drama of Conservation-A Geographic Allegory, 1918 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Writing: "Labor and the War", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Writing: Kapuskasing (Canadian Returned Soldiers Settlement Colony) Data, 1918 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Writing: "Outline for Plan for Employing Returned Soldiers in Utilizing Fuelwood on the White Mountain National Forest, NH and Maine", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Writing: "A Plan for Emergency Fuelwood for Washington, DC", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Writing: "Reconnaissance Plan for Woodlot Development", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Writing: "Reconstruction and Natural Resources", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Writing: "Some Aspects of Forest Management" - Journal of Forestry, 1918 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Writing: Statement by Benton MacKaye, Specialist in Colonization", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Writing: "Suggestions for Marketing Small Timber", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Writing: Synopsis of Colonization of Timberlands", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Writing: "Tentative Plan for Operation by US Wood Fuel Corporation", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Writing: "Utilization of Land for the Soldier and Worker", 1918 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Writing: "The White Mountain Project" Department of Labor, 1918 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Writing: "An Offer: United States Department of Labor to Cooperate with Private Landowners…", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Writing: "A Bill for the Disposition of Returned Soldiers…", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Writing: "Comparative Statement of Kelly and Mondell Bills", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Writing: "Employment and Natural Resources", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Writing: "Employment and Natural Resources" Notes, Data and Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 176, Folder 25)
    - Writing: "The Federal Trade Plan", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 26)
    - Writing: "The First Soldier Colony - Kapuskasing, Canada", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 27)
    - Writing: "Land and Living Costs", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 28)
    - Writing: "The Lesson of Alaska", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 29)
    - Writing: Alaska Data, 1913 (Box 176, Folder 30)
    - Notes: "Alaska, Walter Todd et.al", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 31)
    - Writing: "Making New Opportunities for Employment", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 32)
    - Writing: Memo to the Assistant Secretary re. Colonization Investigation in Alaska, 1919 (Box 176, Folder 33)
    - Writing: "A Plan for Handling the Living Problem", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 34)
    - Writing: "The Plumb Railroad Plan", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 35)
    - Writing: "Power and Living Costs", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 36)
    - Writing: "Real wages Are Lower Now", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 37)
    - Writing: "Unemployment and the 65th Congress", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 38)
    - Writing: "Why Your Dollar Is Worth Less", 1919 (Box 176, Folder 39)
    - Writing: Congressional Bills Authored by Benton MacKaye, 1913-1919 (Box 176, Folder 40)
    - Writing: "Alaska - An Opportunity to Build A Nation", 1920 (Box 176, Folder 41)
    - Writing: "Farm to Consumer Via Postal Motor Service", 1920 (Box 176, Folder 42)
    - Writing: "Feeding the City by Motor Truck", undated (Box 176, Folder 43)
    - Writing: "A Plan for Cooperation Between Farmer and Consumer", 1920 (Box 176, Folder 44)
    - Writing: "Post Office Project" with data, 1919-1920 (Box 176, Folder 45)
    - Writing: "Post Office Project" with data, 1919-1920 (Box 176, Folder 46)
    - Writing: "A Suggested Investigation of Postal Marketing Projects", 1912 (Box 176, Folder 47)
    - Writing: Milwaukee Leader articles, 1920 (Box 176, Folder 48)
    - Writing: Synopsis of Articles on the Northwest Program, 1920 (Box 176, Folder 49)
    - Writing: Milwaukee Leader Editorials, 1920 (Box 176, Folder 50)
    - Writing: "The Northwest Program", 1920 (Box 176, Folder 51)
  - Box: 177, 1921-1929 (Box 177)
    Box: 177
    - Writing: Diary Excerpts, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Writing: "Memorandum of Regional Planning", 1921 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Writing: Disarmament Conference article, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Writing: "The Need for Social Engineering", 1921 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Writing: "A Plan for Developing a Program for Industry in the United States", 1921 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Writing: "Regional Planning and Social Readjustment", 1921 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Writing: Reports on the Lumber Industry, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Writing: River Regulation Work, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Writing: "Waste in the Lumber Industry", 1921 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Draft and Date, undated (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail Inc. Constitution, undated (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS "A Regional Plan for Conserving Natural Resources and Human Labor", 1922 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS "Diary Excerpts", 1921-1925 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS " A Project For An Appalachian Trail", undated (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Writing" Appalachian Trail: Typescript "A Project For An Appalachian Trail, Undated (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "A Project For An Appalachian Trail" in American Institute of Architects Journal, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS "A Project For An Appalachian Trail" - A New Approach to Industrial Problems, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS "A Project For An Appalachian Trail" - A New Approach to Industrial Problems - Memo, 1921 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Writing: "The Trail Out: An Outdoor Survey Of Social Forces", 1922 (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - Writing: Diary Excerpts, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Writing: Kuzbas Project, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Notes: On MacKaye Cottage History, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - Notes: Stratton Mountain Trip, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 23)
    - Writing: "An Outdoor Recreation System", 1922 (Box 177, Folder 24)
    - Writing: "Progress Toward the Appalachian Trail", 1922 (Box 177, Folder 25)
    - Writing: Vermont Trips, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 26)
    - Report: Deerfield Power System with maps and data, 1922 (Box 177, Folder 27)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "Making Geography: A Conservative Survey pf the Appalachian Trail", 1922-1923 (Box 177, Folder 28)
    - Appalachian Trail: "Great Appalachian Trail From New Hampshire To The Carolinas", 1923 (Box 177, Folder 29)
    - Writing: "The Modern Wilderness Industry", 1923 (Box 177, Folder 30)
    - Data: Water Power - Washington, 1923 (Box 177, Folder 31)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "Work Progress on Appalachian Trail Building", 1923 (Box 177, Folder 32)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "Appalachian Power-Servant or Master", 1924 (Box 177, Folder 33)
    - Data: Appalachian Trail: Mileage, 1924 (Box 177, Folder 34)
    - Writing: A Report on A Regional Survey of New York" with maps and data, 1924 (Box 177, Folder 35)
    - Writing: "A Suggested Policy For Approaching The Problem Of Regional Planning In The United States", 1924 (Box 177, Folder 36)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "What Is The Appalachian Trail?", 1924 (Box 177, Folder 37)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: Address to the Appalachian Trail Conference, 1925 (Box 177, Folder 38)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: MS "The Appalachian Project - A First Move In Regional Planning", 1925 (Box 177, Folder 39)
    - Writing: "The Battle of Doodeltown", 1925 (Box 177, Folder 40)
    - Writing: "Memorandum For Percy MacKaye On My Recollection Of My Father's Dramatization Of Buffalo Bill's Wild West…", 1925 (Box 177, Folder 41)
    - Notes: Shirley Christmas Carnival, 1925 (Box 177, Folder 42)
    - Writing: Diary Excerpts on Solar Eclipse, 1925 (Box 177, Folder 43)
    - Notes: Talks given at the Civic Club, 1925 (Box 177, Folder 44)
    - Writing: "The Kidder Mountain Trail", 1926 (Box 177, Folder 45)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "Memorandum For Mr. Roosevelt On Taconic Section Of The Appalachian Trail", 1926 (Box 177, Folder 46)
    - Writing: "The New Northwest Passage", 1926 (Box 177, Folder 47)
    - Report: New York State Report of the Commission of Housing and Regional Planning…, 1926 (Box 177, Folder 48)
    - Notes: On Natural Resources with charts, 1926 (Box 177, Folder 49)
    - Writing: "A Region Equipped For Play", 1926 (Box 177, Folder 50)
    - Writing: "Regional Planning Report On The Archangelskoe Rayon North Caucasus, Russia", 1926 (Box 177, Folder 51)
    - Notes: Walking Trips Shirley, 1926 (Box 177, Folder 52)
    - Writing: "A Boy's Project For A Balanced Civilization", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 53)
    - Writing: "The Cape Cod Region", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 54)
    - Writing: "A Cross-Section Of Massachusetts - Two Possibilities", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 55)
    - Writing: Diary Excerpts, 1927 (Box 177, Folder 56)
    - Writing: Memorandum for W.R. Greeley, 1927 (Box 177, Folder 57)
    - Writing: "Industrial Exploration", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 58)
    - Writing: Party Invitation, 1927 (Box 177, Folder 59)
    - Writing: "The Mohawk Trail", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 60)
    - Writing: "Outdoor Culture", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 61)
    - Writing: "Outdoor Culture" Reprint, 1927 (Box 177, Folder 62)
    - Writing: "A Primer For Regional Planning", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 63)
    - Writing: "Overt Tactics - Common Purpose Of The Militant Suffragists and Railway Brotherhood…", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 64)
    - Writing: Appalachian Trail: "Statement On The Purpose Of The Appalachian Trail", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 65)
    - Writing: "Worcester Talk, Clark University…", 1927 (Box 177, Folder 66)
    - Writing: List of Writings up to 1928 (Box 177, Folder 67)
    - Writing: "The Community Club Of Shirley Center", 1928-1931 (Box 177, Folder 68)
    - Writing: Definition of Regional Planning, 1928-1930 (Box 177, Folder 69)
    - Writing: "Equipping A Region For Play", 1928 (Box 177, Folder 70)
    - Writing: Open Spaces: Letter to Charles S. Bird, undated (Box 177, Folder 71)
    - Writing: Open Spaces: Statement of Job Before Committee on Needs and Uses of Open Spaces, 1928 (Box 177, Folder 72)
    - Writing: Open Spaces: Scheme for Field Work, undated (Box 177, Folder 73)
    - Writing: Open Spaces: Notes for the First Report to the Sub-Committee on Open Spaces, 1928 (Box 177, Folder 74)
    - Writing: Open Spaces: Progress Report, 1928 (Box 177, Folder 75)